[Music]
[Música]
yes
sí
cultured and highlights that I have found I know
culta y resalta que me he encontrado sé
that what I'm going to show you this chair for
que lo que os voy a enseñar esta silla
a week okay I know that what I'm going to
una semanita vale sé que lo que os voy a
show you this chair for a week but I
enseñar esta silla una semanita pero me
liked it so much that I said I'm going to I'm
ha gustado tanto que he dicho lo voy a
going to comment on it in today's live and
lo voy a comentar en el directo de hoy y
also I'm going to record it for an extract
además lo voy a grabar para un extracto
to later receive it no
para luego recibirlo no
and it turns out that
y resulta que
[Music]
[Música]
September 6th was the day
el 6 de septiembre fue el día
in which
en el que se en el que se emite por
the documentary was broadcast for the first time on open television
primera vez en abierto el documental
but of course evidently this has been the
sino claro evidentemente esta ha sido la
second this has been the second
segunda las este ha sido el segundo
program no
programa no
now this has been the second Monday which well
ahora este ha sido el segundo lunes que
last week if I remember
bueno la semana pasada si no recuerdo
correctly it was Wednesday and they don't know when to
mal fue el miércoles y no saben cuándo
square what they don't know how to square it
cuadrar lo que no saben cómo cuadrar lo
because it's complicated because they have
porque está complicado porque tienen
some very powerful competitors and on
unos competidores muy potentes y en este
this occasion because people are already
en esta ocasión por la gente está ya
burned out and people have generated a
quemada y la gente tiene generado un
rejection on Tuesday okay well it turns out
rechazo el martes vale pues resulta ser
that the maestro Joao
que el maestro joao
around q the maestros Joao okay
alrededor de q los maestros joao vale
by the way quite harassing for my
por cierto bastante acosador para mi
taste in some of the maestro's attitudes
gusto en algunas actitudes del maestro
already or not for example this tweet that he posted and
ya o no por ejemplo este tuit que puso y
Sydney I  I'm going to put it here to
sydney yo lo voy a poner aquí para
remember what we saw back in the day but oh
recordar lo que en su día lo vimos pero
well we remember it again no look
bueno lo volvemos a recordar no fíjate
you go you don't have it up the
tú vete tú no lo tiene arriba la marea
fuchsia tide tonight everyone with Jorge Javier
fucsia esta noche todos con jorge javier
the day of the survivor final I
el día de la final de supervivientes
don't have a [ __ ] I don't have it
no tengo [__] no lo tengo
another moreno
otra moreno
to start the childishness of the case not
para empezar lo infantil del caso no
to start starting with the childish and
para empezar empezando por lo infantil y
the second thing is that he is a bit of a stalker uncle
lo segundo que es un poco acosador tío
already more always always master joao I have
ya más siempre siempre maestro joao
seen him messing with women in
lo he visto metiéndose con mujeres de
a very orenda way I remember the
una forma muy orenda me acuerdo con el
subject of adhara that you have two videos on
tema de adhara que tenéis dos vídeos en
my main channel that are two
mi canal principal que son dos vídeos ya
old videos I think the videos are from
antiguos creo que los vídeos son del
2019 okay don't see when he decided to
2019 vale que no vea cuando le dio por a
give it don't see what he decided to have won I do
dar a no vean la que le dio por haber
n't know if it's an obsession
ganador ya no sé si es obsesión
let me see in the end what they have advertising for me
me permita ver al final lo me tienen
hahahahaha
jajajajaja
/ announce ads for when they run out of
/ anuncia anuncios para cuando se queden
advertising to fill what
sin anunciando para rellenar qué
for them to call him I don't know if
para que lo llamen ya no sé si estaba
the obsession was so much that they call him I
tanto la obsesión como para que lo
think it's more so that they call him
yo creo que es más para que lo llamen
than anything else uncle
que otra cosa tío
call them joaquín that no  He likes what is
llámalos joaquín que no le gusta lo que
called Joaquín, he has nothing of teachers, we
se llama joaquín es que de maestros no
call them teacher, teacher,
tiene nada les decimos maestro maestro
I do it because he is a man of
yo hago porque es un hombre de
television characters 23, but of the
personajes de la tele 23 pero del
teacher that this man has, what
maestro que tiene este hombre ya qué
profession does this man have, this man,
profesión tiene este hombre este hombre
what he had the luck to do
lo que tuvo la suerte de hacer lo que
with the fairies, with the
hizo con lo de las hadas con lo de la
colors, it was divine, my goodness,
colores era divino madre mía
the truth is, and it came from a traca, in less than
la verdad y vino de traca en menos más
that, today it is removed or not,
que eso ya día de hoy está quita o no
that still exists, says Milanese, so much, so
eso todavía existe dice milanés tanta
much fixation with humiliating women
tanta fijación con humilla a las mujeres
who have various rights, it smells like having
que tienen varios derechos huele a tener
some kind of trauma from Saddam, of assets
algún tipo de trauma de sadam de haberes
that women are always the victims, I don't
que siempre son mujeres las víctimas no
know why, I don't know if it is the
sé por qué no sé si es que las más
weakest or not, but this thing about the facts,
débiles o que no pero esto de los hechos
this thing about selling,
esto de vender
look and 8, let it be a thing, look,
mirad y 8 que sea una cosa mira
teacher of 800 euros, you are worth it,
maestro de 800 euros vales
look for this clip, okay, teacher, I make 800 euros,
buscar este clip vale maestro yo hago
look for them on Google, okay, watch
800 euros buscarlos en google vale mirar
this video, man,
este vídeo tío
the system, watch this video, okay, it's on
el sistema mirar este vídeo vale está en
YouTube, look
youtube mira
because you have immediate access
porque tienes acceso
and we are waiting for you,
y te estamos esperando
although apart from noticing improvement, I
aunque aparte de que note mejoría pero
continue reading the letters to a lady,
continuo leyendo las cartas a una señora
look,
mira
a heart technique from Senegal, it is here you
un corazón técnica de senegal está aquí
have it  heart doesn't reduce them it's that I have a
lo tienes corazón no las reduce es que
prosthesis and don't worry because I'm
tengo prótesis y no te preocupes porque
going to make the cut and also since you
voy a hacer el corte y además como tú ya
no longer worry about your health now I'm
no te preocupes por tu salud que ahora
going to have here a couple of cards already in the
voy a tener yo aquí un par de cartas ya
back fix it you have so to speak the
atrás arregla tienes por así decirlo la
prayer on top this will open it and this will
oración encima esto te la abre y esto te
protect you more quickly you see you know
protege con más rapidez verás sabe
YouTube now I'm going to put a
youtube yo ahora te pongo un par de un
couple of cards here and now you have
par de cartas por aquí y ya te tienes
a prosthesis so don't worry that they're
una prótesis por no te preocupes que te
going to remove it and a
la van a quitar y te va a crecer un
real bone will grow okay
hueso real vale
[Music]
[Música]
I have made here a little pepper salt
yo he hecho aquí un poco de pimienta sal
here there's a glass
aquí hay una copa
look you will see
mira verá
[Music]
[Música]
the air will go
el aire irá
Marleny and thank you very much look look
marleny y muchas gracias mira mira
there it is cut my life may
ahí está cortado vida mía
God bless you
que dios te bendiga
so far the evil eye has been removed okay
hasta ahora quitado el mal de ojo vale
let's see interest now let's see
vamos a ver interés ahora vamos a ver
but if you worked with that person who we
pero si trabajaste con esa persona que
better not name because he plays the
mejor no la nombramos porque toca las
magic of Crete but look what he has
magias de creta pero mira lo que te ha
done to you look what he speaks to you
liado a ti mira lo que te habla te mira
the devil is looking at you I
el demonio
am here honey
estoy aquí cariño
teacher this guy okay you go and
profesora este tío vale que vete tú a
know where this guy came from
saber de dónde salió este tío
also last week for me
también la semana pasada para mí
from Iraq  the Spanish
de irak el españo
but I didn't see where they have to give
pero no vi a dónde tienen que dar
Marlene and a huge hug
marlene y un abrazo enorme
courage exam and everything and then what he
valor examen y todo y entonces que le
gave me he told me that I already had
dio me dijo que ya tenía yo la salud de
my son's health but that while he does
mi hijo pero que mientras
n't want to see me with his girlfriend he
no quiere verme con la novia
tells him that but I really shoot how
le dice que pero tiro de verdad que
angry it makes me the people who take
rabia me da las personas que se
advantage of one of the
aprovechan de una de las de una de las
most vulnerable parts of society which
partes de la sociedad más vulnerables
are our elders what we
que son nuestros mayores chivas lo que
owe them everything okay there are the children
les debemos todo vale ya están los niños
and then there are our elders also
y luego están nuestros mayores también
the people who take advantage of the
las personas que se aprovechan de la
innocence many times they owe culture of
inocencia muchas veces deben cultura de
the elderly
las personas mayores
okay there are those in there are many who
vale que los hay en los hay muchos que
take advantage of the innocence of
se aprovechan de la inocencia de
our elders who brainwash them and
nuestros mayores que les comen el coco y
are very vulnerable not to the ladies
son muy vulnerables no a las señoras
trusting us that they are going to call this
confiándonos en que van a llamar a este
man and that this man will move
señor y que este señor pues va a mover
the cards and the son will
las cartas y ya el hijo le va a volver a
speak to him again and the ladies are saying
hablar y están los señora diciendo
man but if last week I called you
hombre pero si la semana pasada te llame
last week I called you and man
la semana pasada te llame y hombre
last week I had my and my son
la semana pasada tenía mi y mi hijo
still won't speak to me because if not if not we are not
sigue sin hablarme porque si no si no no
going to do anything I understand the
vamos a hacer nada yo entiendo la
situation I have already said the first thing
situación ya he dicho el que lo primero
that came out  here it has been the devil
que te ha salido aquí ha sido el [__]
but we are going to hold another court
pero vamos a hacer otra corte
immediately I need it to be ruled out
inmediatamente necesito que se descarte
yes an immediate one and they won't let you
eso sí una inmediata y no te dejan
how strong
qué fuerte
thank you very much and
muchas gracias y
rolling with laughter
revolviéndose de la risa
[Music]
[Música]
what you did with the letter from the affected party
lo que hiciste tú con carta del afectado
look how sad Maria Esther for knocking on
fíjate qué pena maría esther por tocar
that door my daughter there you can't
aquella puerta hija mía ahí no se puede
name a
nombrar
teacher look honey on the road more and
profesor mira cariño sobre el camino
more among novice help him if you
cada vez más entre novato ayúdelo si me
let me I'm going to do it my love as
dejas lo voy a hacer cariño mío yo en
soon as you let me I'll do it look don't
cuanto a tú me dejes lo hago mira no
talk now honey don't cross your
hables ahora cariño no cruces las
legs I
piernas
'm doing this already this has been removed from
estoy esto ya esto lo han quitado de la
television no longer this will be prohibited I
tele ya no esto estará prohibido me
imagine no
imagino no
besides I'm going to make a decree I'm also
además le voy a hacer un decreto también
going to put my hands on him look at the
voy a poner mis manos encima mira la
scissors
tijera
cut the bad
corta lo malo
[Music]
[Música]
while the albos
mientras los albos
this is still serious
esto sigue en serio
but done like
pero hecho como
but this as a base as it is allowed
pero esto como base como está permitido
this
esto
I think they should put a
yo creo que deberían ponerle aquí un
sign here that says this fiction or something like
cartelito que digan esto ficción o algo
that now each one who calls under their own
así ya cada uno que llame bajo su
responsibility
responsabilidad
people really call it believing
lo llaman de verdad la gente creyendo
that this is true
que esto es verdad
and let's see let's
y
see about the 800 euros where in
a ver a ver lo de los 800 euros en qué
what minutes ago is
parte en que minutos atrás
this  note that
esta nota
people see it here in the comments they
lo ve la gente aquí en los comentarios
are saying the same thing as me
está diciendo lo mismo que yo
this is not reportable
esto no es denunciable
but
pero
now I'm going to do something to you you know
ahora te voy a hacer una cosa tú sabes
that I have helped you you already know it and I'm
que yo te ha ayudado ya tú lo sabes y
going to continue helping you the best and
voy a seguir ayudando te lo mejor y
now it hurts me a lot this is the
ahora me duele mucho esto es lo
important thing but I'm going to give you a guarantee
importante pero te voy a es un aval
now I'm going to get you
ahora te voy a
89 euros
89 euros
819 euros I
819 euros
don't know where I'm going to get it from
no sé de dónde lo voy a sacar
but I'm going to tell you you know what's the
pero te voy a decir sabéis que es lo
worst thing
peor
you know what's the worst thing is that in this
sabéis que es lo peor que en esta
discussion that you're going to see now that he has
discusión que vais a ver ahora que tiene
with albert the guy boasts of having money
con albert el tío presume de tener pasta
look he's missing in blackberries I support Rocío in the
mira falta en moras apoyo a rocío en el
name of Pedro okay and he tells him Albert
nombre de pedro vale y le dice albert
Hall and teacher a fan like you and he hasn't
hall y maestro un fan como usted y no ha
even paid my Tele Plus to watch
pagado ni siquiera mi tele plus para ver
the series that he has to wait for you to
la serie que tiene que esperar a que las
put them on open to see it what a
pongas en abierto para verla qué
disappointment two months ago you have those
decepción hace dos meses que tiene esos
episodes on the platform pay a
episodios en la plataforma pague un
little man don't be stingy and
poquito hombre no sea tacaño y le
the teacher answers him already or ha ha ha ha I've
contesta el maestro ya o ja ja ja ja he
seen everything car and thank god I have enough left
visto todo car y gracias a dios me sobra
to subscribe to that and everything that
para abonar me a eso y a todo lo que
comes out my queen Rocío
salga mi reina rocío
on top  presumptuous week that has
encima semana presumida que le sobra el
money to spare in case you are a healer who
dinero por si tú eres un sanador que
takes four cards and moves them, don't
coges cuatro cartas y las mueve no le
charge anyone
cobre a nadie
man if you are miraculous
hombre si eres milagroso
if he is miraculous either if we take a
si él es milagroso ya sea si cogemos una
scissor and say
tijera y dice
cut the oval and cut the good thing [ __ ]
corto el óvalo y corto lo bueno [__]
then don't charge people that's why
pues no le cobre a la gente por eso
okay it's that
vale
the trinquets is that you have to
es que los trinquets es que hay que
have balls to call the agent
tener huevos para llamar tu al agente
trim kers you
trim kers
have to have balls for this man to
hay que tener huevos para que este señor
call you trim care you have to
te llame trim care
have them you have to have
hay que tenerlos
huge ones
hay que tener los enormes
for this day to trinquet me
para que este día me trinquete
it's that they don't have a [ __ ] clue and they
es que no tienen ni [__] idea y se
pronounce themselves giving fake news hahaha
pronuncian dando noticias fake jajaja
trim kers I would invite you to go [ __ ]
trim kers te invitaría a ir a tomar por
yourself Albert tells him I wouldn't invite you to go
culo le dice albert no te invitaría a ir
[ __ ] yourself but since you like to
a tomar por culo pero como te gusta
read them it's not a good idea good night
leerlos no es buena idea buenas noches
psychics
videntes
here the obvious ones are sleeping with
aquí los evidentes se la está tirando el
Albert no also I don't like to read
albert no también no me gusta leer los
other people's I think
de los demás creo que está más
your little pen is more used to it
acostumbrado tu plumilla
pluvials seeing
pluviales al ver
Albert has a real profession
albert tiene una profesión de verdad
Joaquín seeing has a
joaquín al ver tiene una profesión de
real profession for which he has studied he has
verdad para la que ha estudiado
already passed master he has already passed to  benghazi having already put
ya pasó maestro ya pasó a bengasi ya
aside your series that I have
habiendo lado tu serie que luego se la
to explain to him later and he won't like it
tengo que explicar yo y no le gustará
and welcomed it and he started whining
y acogido y se ha puesto a lloriquear
saying the supposed journalist albert
diciendo el supuesto periodista albert
domènech
domènech
criticizing that I haven't seen the documentary series
criticando que no he visto el docu serie
of dew when it's enough to read my twitter
de rocío cuando basta leer mi twitter
to see how I comment on all the
para ver cómo comento todos los
chapters if they don't know how to write
capítulos si es que no saben escribir yo
if there is a spelling mistake that he hasn't
si existe una falta ortografía que no ha
written has never set foot in a school in his
escrito no ha pisado un colegio en la
life this man anyway that's how it goes with
vida este hombre en fin así va la cosa
some professionals because the
en algunos profesionales porque el
professional is the one who letters
profesional es el que le cartas
nothing more to add your honor we hope you
nada más que añadir señoría esperamos
rectify your mistake no
que rectifique su error no
and he says to her when he sees that they have fallen in love
y le dice al ver que se han enamorado
merche I was the best journalist in my
merche fui el mejor periodista de mi
course after avilés come on teacher
curso después de avilés venga maestro
try it with someone else because with me they won't give you
inténtelo con otro que conmigo no le dan
the chair in the debate that I don't sell
la silla en el debate que yo no vendo
bessis and the teacher says for you of course they don't
bessis y le dice el maestro por ti claro
give anything not a cent ha ha ha ha
que no dan nada ni un céntimo ja ja ja
teacher
maestro
what the [ __ ] are you talking about and he's
qué [__] estás hablando y se está
trying to compare himself to a professional
intentando comparar con un profesional
for you they don't give anything not a cent but
por ti no dan nada ni un céntimo pero
teacher you have to mess with
maestro que te tienes que meter con la
people what do you have to
gente que tiene usted que
mess with anything for what  they will call you the
meterte con nada para que te llamarán el
year in the year 2019 of a
año en el año 2019 de un programa de
youtube program that they tried to make a program
youtube que intentaron hacer un programa
on youtube called bámbola that
en youtube que se llama bámbola que no
the microphones could not even be heard well and
se escuchaban ni bien los micrófonos y
you went for being on twitter putting I
tú fuiste por estar en twitter metiendo
have nothing that was harassment and demolition that is why they
tengo nada que era acoso y derribo por
call you and now they are
eso a ti te llaman y ahora te están
positioning you so that they call you without any more
posicionando para que te llamen sin más
tact if you had to defend Rocío
tino si tuvieras que defender a rocío
Flores to defend aunts chaqueta who was
flores a defender tías chaqueta que era
a jacket
un chaqueta
that for albert they do not give a cent
que por albert no dan ni un céntimo
albert has a
albert tiene una profesión
stable and firm profession okay albert has a
estable y firme vale albert tiene una
profession
profesión
that does not depend on the issues
que no depende de los temas
albert has his contract in his newspaper
albert tiene su contrato en su periódico
and if not in that one in another and if not in another
y si no en ese en otro y si no en otro
in another and in another in another and on
en otro y en otro en otro y en
television and wherever for being a
televisión y en donde quiera por ser
journalist for the career that you have you or
periodista por la carrera que tiene ti o
you depend
tú dependes
on the issues
de los temas
you depend on the issues
tu depende de los temas
the characters these are broken toys
los personajes estos sois juguetes rotos
and it depends on you to put them in a
y os depende de que los metan en un
reality show of cometan in a big
reality de cometan en una casa de gran
brother house to put them in I don't know what
hermano de que los metan en un no sé qué
and when the years go by you have to
y cuando se os pasan los años tenéis que
be  crawling
estar arrastrándose
licking their feet of the opinion that
lamiendo los pies de la opinión que
they want to give
quieran que dei
how are you going to compare yourself to a person who
cómo te vas a comparar con una persona
has a career
que tiene una carrera
that you have been reading letters and not in
que tú has estado leyendo cartas y no en
emails
correos
this seems crazy to me
esto me parece de locos
you can believe this there are people who
tú puedes creer así hay gente que se
created their claws like well that they believe it
crearon sus garras como bueno que se lo
but of course the level is
crea pero claro el nivel es
this is the level of the people who
este es el nivel de las personas que
support Rocío Carrasco
apoyan a rocío carrasco
okay
vale
until there is false information about
hasta que haya una información falsa de
me
mí
but surely
pero seguramente
surely he would not give
seguramente él no diera informaciones
false information surely he moves you three or
falsas seguramente él te mueve tres o
four cards and he cures the prosthesis of
cuatro cartas y le cura la prótesis a
the ladies who call on the phone his
las señoras que llaman por teléfono sus
information is true okay and I have
informaciones son verídicas vale y te he
answered you I hope that you do not invent the rest
respondido espero que las demás no te
too
las inventes también
and here when I see it he ends up bursting his
y aquí al ver ya le termina de reventar
teeth
los dientes
name if I made up things I would have shielded myself I
nombre si me inventara cosas habría
would have studied clairvoyance
escudado habría estudiado videncia
if I made up things I would have studied
si me inventara cosas habría estudiado
evidence
evidencia
put it all over your mouth here when you see what he
pon en toda la boca aquí al ver lo que
is telling you
le está diciendo
you have lived by making up things by
tú has vivido de inventarte cosas
making up that he is going to bring
de inventarte que que le va a traer
loose I do not know who who cuts the thread
suelta no sé quién que le corta el hilo
of the evil eye but he lost
de mal de ojo pero perdió
man for God and feel proud that he
hombre por dios y sentirte orgulloso de
is loaded
que está forrado
feel proud that you have money to spare
sentirte orgulloso de que te sobra el
a little dignity
un poquito de dignidad
[Music]
[Música]